<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="4.2.0">Jekyll</generator><link href="http://coastrangereader.github.io/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="http://coastrangereader.github.io/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2021-10-24T17:30:15-07:00</updated><id>http://coastrangereader.github.io/feed.xml</id><title type="html">The Coast Range Reader</title><subtitle>Stories and ideas for west Oregonians.</subtitle><entry><title type="html">The Book of Dults</title><link href="http://coastrangereader.github.io/2021/10/23/book-of-dults/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="The Book of Dults" /><published>2021-10-23T04:00:00-07:00</published><updated>2021-10-23T04:00:00-07:00</updated><id>http://coastrangereader.github.io/2021/10/23/book-of-dults</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://coastrangereader.github.io/2021/10/23/book-of-dults/">&lt;div class=&quot;imgcap_noborder&quot;&gt;
	&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/book-of-dults/dults-cover.png&quot; width=&quot;50%&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Welcome to the rough guide of the strange world of dults. Have you ever found yourself surrounded by a large herd of older people? Have you ever been confuserd by the way some of them tried to engage with you? Have you ever wondered why some behave so strangely when they talk to you? Then this guide is just what you need! It will identify many of the dults you might encounter on a typical day and you will learn how to react to their strange behaviors. Remember, most dults aren’t dangerous, they’re just weird! Let’s get started…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;imgcap_noborder&quot; style=&quot;display: block; margin-left: auto; margin-right: auto; width:100%;margin-bottom: 200px; margin-top: 50px&quot;&gt;
    &lt;a href=&quot;../../../../files/book-of-dults-preview.pdf&quot; id=&quot;featuredlink&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; style=&quot;margin-right: 10px;&quot;&gt;Read the Book of Dults&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">A lighthearted collaboration between my father and I from a few years ago. It&apos;s a field guide to the world of grown ups, written for kids.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Introducing the Coast Range Reader</title><link href="http://coastrangereader.github.io/2021/10/22/introducing-crr/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Introducing the Coast Range Reader" /><published>2021-10-22T04:00:00-07:00</published><updated>2021-10-22T04:00:00-07:00</updated><id>http://coastrangereader.github.io/2021/10/22/introducing-crr</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://coastrangereader.github.io/2021/10/22/introducing-crr/">&lt;div class=&quot;imgcap_noborder&quot;&gt;
  &lt;img src=&quot;/assets/profile_picture.png&quot; width=&quot;100%&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I recently made a resolution to stop reading the news entirely. It was not out of a desire to become less cultured, or less responsible, but rather it began as a vague impression that reading the news was making me an unfocused and impotent creature. A creature too attached to storylines over which I had rather little agency. From there, it grew into a suspicion that the problem was not &lt;em&gt;the&lt;/em&gt; news, but &lt;em&gt;which&lt;/em&gt; news. In other words, my attention at the time was directed expressly at world and national affairs. While I could articulate with some clarity the latest scandal occurring in Washington, I was ignorant as to the major changes in the coast range region of Oregon where I live.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And so I shifted my attention.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I began by trying to place the coast range within the world as a whole. What is our role? How are we changing? In what ways is our culture commendable, and in what ways are we blind? I also tried to learn something about patterns in commerce, education, community, and so forth. The things that would ordinarily appear from time to time in a local newspaper.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Talk a bit more about the value of literary ideas, stories, artifacts, pictures. Bower bird stuff.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Still figuring out the purpose of this magazine. It should be more of a literary and artistic publication than a news source. But it should permit rapid, low-resolution posts as well as longer essay-like posts. I like the structure of the prairie home companion – but as a magazine. Anyways, writing the rest of this post will allow me to clarify such things.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">Introducing a new lightweight literary publication to the world.</summary></entry></feed>